

JIHYUN LEE

I am interested in video games, and I like to work with various people.

My Comfortable Programming language is C, and I have been using C language for 4 years.

I am the type of the person who is challenging, creative, and extrovert.

PERSONAL DATA

Date of birth: 10/10/1996 Place of birth: Incheon

Nationality: Republic of Korea

Marital status: Single

CONTACT

878, Jangjae-ro Gyeyang-gu, SeoHae APT 107/1702 Incheon, Republic of Korea 21035

Email: ph4020@hanmail.net Telephone: +82 10 9426 0682

LANGUAGES

Korean **IIII**English **III**German **III**

HOBBIES

Vigeo Game Travel

OTHERS

Driving license Class B TOEFL 80 Opic IM

CAREER

Working student in Sogang University 03/2017 - 07/2020 35, Baekbeom-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea

- Marketer in Yellow Green
- LAB Manager in Engineering Faculty
- Mentor in Python course
- Researcher in Office of international Affair
- Supporter in Youth Education center

Internship in Oneday Korea 07/2019 - 08/2019 510, Tongil-ro, Seodaemun-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea

- Natural Language Programmer
- Web Programmer
- Web Designer

EDUCATION

K-move Training course	07/2020 - 12/2020
Sogang University	03/2015 - 08/2020
Brno University of Technology	09/2019 - 02/2020
Giic AR/VR Hackerway	11/2018
Smilegate Server Development Camp	01/2017 - 02/2017

FURTHER EDUCATION

Choir of Sogang University 03/2015 - 02/2017 Association of Student 03/2015 - 02/2016

KNOWLEDGE

Programming Language: C/C++, Python, Java Information processing Compuster Specialist in Spreadsheet & Database Word Processor Specialist Computer Graphics Operation Web Design

August 06, 2020 Lilhyun

CAREER

Working student in Sogang University

03/2017 - 07/2020

- Marketer in Yellow Green
 - Make Animation Books
 - Promote on SNS
 - Test Application
 - Plan Events
 - Research Books
- LAB Manager in Engineering Faculty
- Mentor in Python course
- Researcher in Office of international Affair
 - Research for Study Abroad
 - Translate Non-Korean Documents
- Supporter in Youth Education center
 - Teach Children
 - Child : Fairy tale

Elementary: Korean and Mathmatics

High: Japanese

07/2019 - 08/2019

Internship in Oneday Korea

- Natural Language Programmer
 - Machine Learning: RASA
- Web Programmer
 - Languege: Python
- Web Designer
 - Javascript, CSS

EDUCATION

K-move Training course, Seoul, Republic of Korea

- German language and culture
- Business English
- JAVA Programming

Sogang University, Seoul, Republic of Korea

- Major: Computer Science and Engineering
- ▶ Bachelor thesis: Development of flight baggage test service through object detection
- Complete a course in teacher education
- Scholarship: Alumni Association in Computer Engineering / 8 Semester (03/2015 02/2020)

Brno University of Technology, Brno, Czech Republic

- Studying Abroad
- Major: Faculty of Information Technology
- Scholarship : Exchange Student Scholarship

Giic AR/VR Hackerway, Hansung University, Seoul, Republic of Korea

AR/VR Programming

Smilegate Server Development Camp, Pangyi, Republic of Korea

Front Developer

FURTHER EDUCATION

Choir of Sogang University

- Vice-president
- ▶ Soprano Ⅱ
- Plan Schedule
- Promote Events
- Manage members

Association of Student in Computer Engineering

- Secretary
- Manage Schedule
- Plan Events

Volunteering

IT Education in Laos PDR

07/2017 - 08/2017

- Educate Programming
 - Programming Tool : Applnventor
- Educate Video Editing
 - Editor : Vegas
- Change Cultures
 - Introduce Korean cultures
 - Make Korean traditional foods
 - Experience Korean traditional games

2018 PyeongChang Olympics and Paralympics

- Technical service with Samsung, KT, and Monami
- Apply tickets for customers' requests
- Connect managers
- Support events

01/2018 - 03/2018